Don't get me wrong.
I know this is a sad day
But still, I figured they'd at least put up a poster saying
"Welcome back, Mercedes."
I mean, look, no confetti.
No red carpet even though I called.
- I'm the biggest Broadway Star
- I'm the biggest recording artist
- What the hell?!
- What happened?!
- I would be so excited.
- I'm excited.
- Are you nervous?
- I mean, like, a little.
Of course she is!
- It's your Broadway debut!
- I know!
Oh, my God.
I can't wait
- for that album to drop.
- Thank you.
I mean, come on. She wrote a couple of songs.
Big whoop.
So what? She got cast
What a surprise.
There's only one way
Sit front and center in the Rachel chair.
Greet each other.
Hello, Rachel.
I am so happy to hear
Oh, thank you so much, Mercedes.
And you are looking well.
Thank you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'll make my way to the back of the bus.
100 lessons.
Hey, can I get Finn's plaque when we clear this place out?
No, the plaque stays here.
Lillian and Finn
It means so much to me
To sit in this room one last time
Your assignment is to sing
Way back in the old days when I started the glee club,
I would give an assignment, and then I would...
I would give a little demonstration
Yeah!
See, you all cheer now,
Okay, no hip-hop today, Santana.
However, I have asked a very special person to come join me.
And it seemed appropriate since her contributions
Please welcome, all the way from Broadway,
Miss April Rhodes!
Hey, y'all!
You know, she once taught me how to shoplift meat
- in my vagina.
- Ew.
Right?
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com
So, Mr. Moneybags says to me, he says,
"April Rhodes, you sing like an angel
"and make love like a tiger.
"But the old ball and chain's got your number.
So I'm afraid
I gots to set you loose."
So, you know what he did?
He bought me an island!
That's right.
I own my own island
Santa Abrilrodeo.
It's not war-torn or filled with landslides
Just me and my manservant Kadeem.
With long, sensuous nights
Okay, thank you, April, for that...
Amen!
Amen, but...
'Cause we are about to pop the cork with some bubbly.
But don't worry, this Spumante is virgin.
Probably like you will be
Anyways...
Will and I want you
New Directions! ever did.
Wait a second, the New
Directions! never sang
"Raise Your Glass."
The Warblers did that.
I was wondering why it didn't annoy me
I always have had a soft spot in my heart
- Well...
- Honk!
Hit it, boys.
♪ Right, right, turn off the lights ♪
♪ We're gonna lose our minds tonight ♪
♪ What's the deal, yo? ♪
Yeah!
♪ I love when it's all too much ♪
♪ 5:00 a.m. turn the radio up ♪
♪ Where's the rock and roll? ♪
♪ Nar-na-nar-na-nar-nar, whoa! ♪
♪ Party crasher, panty snatcher ♪
♪ Call me up if you're a gangsta ♪
Yeah!
♪ Don't be fancy ♪
♪ Just get dancing ♪
♪ Why so serious? ♪
♪ So raise your glass if you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be, never be anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty gritty dirty little freaks ♪
♪ Won't you come on and come on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come on and raise your glass ♪
Oh, no.
My glass is empty.
That sucks.
♪ So if you're too school for cool ♪
♪ And you're treated like a fool ♪
♪ Treated like a fool ♪
♪ You can choose to let it go ♪
♪ Choose to let it go ♪
♪ We can always, we can always ♪
♪ Party on our own ♪
♪ So raise your ♪
♪ So raise your glass ♪
♪ If you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be, never be anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty gritty ♪
♪ And nitty gritty dirty little freaks ♪
♪ Won't you come on and come on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come on and raise your glass ♪
♪ For me ♪ Just come on and come on and raise your glass ♪
♪ For me. ♪
I was The Saw.
That's what they called me.
I sliced through this school
Dude got in my way?
Sawed him.
Set my sights on a chick?
Sawed her.
It would've been like a horror movie if I wasn't so awesome.
But that guy's gone now.
I have a purpose.
To defend our great country with my superior airpower.
I don't look back.
The past is dead to me.
Except for maybe just one thing.
Hey, Puck.
Hey.
So, uh, have you noticed how hot I look in my uniform?
It does look a little bit itchy.
Are you serious or...?
I'm just kidding.
You look really handsome.
It's not just the uniform, either.
You've got this newfound confidence about you.
So, um,
I'm not sure.
Maybe we could go to Breadstix.
Mull some potentials.
You know it's my tickle spot!
Hi.
I got bored sitting at the hotel.
Who's this?
Puck, this is my boyfriend.
Biff Macintosh.
Like the Apple?
Yeah, exactly like it.
My family planted the first
Macintosh apple orchard
So, every time you have one of our apples,
This is my very old,
Noah Puckerman.
Puck, Puckerman.
Is that Jewish?
She never told you about me?
How long you been going out?
- About three months.
- Well, you know,
Quinn doesn't really like to talk about her past,
- as you said it might be.
- Mmm.
I said, "If you want to meet Mother,
I have to really get to know you first."
Wait, you call your mother
"Mother"?
I need to show Biff the auditorium.
Thank you so much.
It's been great talking to you, Puck.
It was good to meet you.
Nice uniform.
Looks a little itchy, though.
Hey. I've been looking for you everywhere.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to prove the Reimann hypothesis.
Who's forcing you to do this?
My colleagues at M.I.T.
They said I had the most gifted mind in a generation.
Miss Pierce?
What's five billion,752 million,
293 thousand 288
715 thousand,548?
I don't know. Six?
I just wish that I could have my old life back,
Well,
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Baby, can't you see ♪
♪ I'm calling ♪
♪ A guy like you ♪
♪ Should wear a warning ♪
♪ It's dangerous ♪
♪ I'm falling ♪
♪ There's no escape ♪
♪ I can't wait ♪
♪ I need a hit ♪
♪ Baby, give me it ♪
♪ You're dangerous,
I'm loving it ♪
♪ Too high, can't come down ♪
♪ It's in the air and it's all around ♪
♪ Can you feel me now? ♪
♪ With a taste of your lips,
I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic,
I'm slipping under ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Ho, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ With a taste of your lips,
I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic,
I'm slipping under ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ Intoxicate me now ♪
♪ With your loving now ♪
♪ I think I'm ready now,
I think I'm ready now ♪
♪ Intoxicate me now ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ With your loving now ♪
♪ I think I'm ready now ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh. ♪
That is what I'm
What did you think,
Mr. Preppy McDimplebutt?
Oh, I thought it was, um,
Dude, you were texting the whole time.
Yeah, well, he's very busy.
He's, um, president of a... of a secret society
You were great.
Oh.
Well, you were amazing as usual.
No, I wasn't.
During the bridge,
I was out of sync
What are you talking about?
You're the most amazing dancer
I've ever met.
No, I need to focus on what I'm good at.
Quantitative algorithms.
And if there's any time left in the day,
Internet talk show.
♪ Fondue for Two,
Fondue for Two ♪
♪ That's some hot dish ♪
♪ Fondue for Two. ♪
Hello, America.
I'm Brittany S. Pierce,
I'm a genius.
Tonight's guests are two of McKinley's
Mercedes Jones and Rachel Berry.
- Question, Rachel.
- Yes.
You're currently rehearsing for
You're also working full-time
That's correct.
Would you agree that it's
Uh, no, I-I just...
When are the lies going to stop?
You don't even live in New York.
I'm not even sure you've been to New York.
Brittany, we went to New York together.
Don't change the subject.
Are your cats making out?
Yes, they are.
Mercedes, how would you respond to the rumors
- that you're a really good dancer...
- Ha!
But you hid the fact the entire time
- "Park and Bark"?
- No comment.
Good. Last question.
Do you know what song you're going to sing
Yes. "Defying Gravity."
What?!
No, you can't sing that song.
Kurt and I are singing it, but we're switching parts
That's not reinventing a song.
You can't do that.
You know what, Mercedes?
Why don't we settle this the old-fashioned way?
A diva-off?
Oh, hell to the yes.
It's on.
I've never really noticed because I haven't spent
It means so much to me that you came back here.
You know, it makes us feel so much more real.
Yeah, well, we are very real.
I love you, Quinn, and I want to
Well, what do you want to know?
I can tell you so many things,
Oh, no, not you.
Hey, guys.
Come here. Yeah, you.
Come on.
Hey, guys.
Hi. Santana Lopez.
Word on the street is that you're old money.
I'm a lesbian, but I'm totally into that.
Mike Chang, Asian dancer.
And I'm Artie Abrams.
I may look like
So, what about Quinn?
How would you describe her
She's constantly surprising you.
Like, one year, she showed up to school in the fall
She dyed her hair pink, she got a Ryan Seacrest tattoo,
Hold on one second.
Piano?
They're-They're messing with you. Honey, I forgot
Oh, absolutely.
I'll go get it
No worries.
What the hell was that?
I am trying to present myself in a particular way.
Biff's family is Philadelphia
Main Line society,
How do you cover up the tattoo, you know?
Like, what? Magic?
I pay my roommate to apply three coats of cover-up makeup
Does he know about us?
About Beth?
I will tell him everything when I'm ready.
The agreement clearly states
Charitable Foundation...
"for the maintenance and operation of this facility
Which means?
Which means, as long
I gets to say who performs there.
If you'd like to start paying for it...
We can't do that.
School doesn't have the money.
Then it sounds to me like the glee club is saved
I will have my team review this and get back to you tomorrow.
Uh, and let's hold off on any official announcements
Let's get some box wine to celebrate!
Wow!
Becky.
There's something fishy going on around here.
We're gonna get to the bottom of it.
All right, everybody,
I wish I could say that this week isn't about
And apparently, the only song
Wait. So we have to listen to Kurt shred that note again?
For the millionth time,
I did it on purpose.
And after we're done singing the song,
Who is the true star of the glee club,
All I've ever wanted in here was to feel chosen.
It's funny, even now,
♪ Something has changed within me ♪
♪ Something is not the same ♪
♪ I'm through with playing by the rules ♪
♪ Of someone else's game ♪
♪ Too late for second-guessing ♪
♪ Too late to go back to sleep ♪
♪ It's time to trust my instincts ♪
♪ Close my eyes and leap ♪
♪ It's time to try ♪
♪ Defying gravity ♪
♪ I think I'll try ♪
♪ Kiss me good-bye ♪
♪ I'm defying gravity ♪
♪ And you won't bring me down ♪
♪ No... ♪
♪ I'm through accepting limits ♪
♪ 'Cause someone says they're so ♪
♪ Some things I cannot change ♪
♪ But till I try
I'll never know ♪
♪ Too long I've been afraid of losing love ♪
♪ I guess I've lost ♪
♪ Well, if that's love, it comes at ♪
♪ Much too high a cost ♪
♪ I'd sooner buy ♪
♪ Defying gravity ♪
♪ Kiss me good-bye ♪
♪ I'm defying gravity ♪
♪ I think I'll try ♪
♪ Defying gravity ♪
♪ And you won't bring me down ♪
♪ I'd sooner buy ♪
♪ Defying gravity ♪
♪ Kiss me good-bye ♪
♪ I'm defying gravity ♪
♪ I think I'll try ♪
♪ Defying gravity ♪
♪ And you won't bring me down ♪
♪ Bring me down! ♪
♪ Down... ♪
Bravo!
The song should be on the Broadway.
All right, let's stop
It's time to vote.
Actually, let's just take a beat and...
We'll sleep on it
But today, right now,
Knight takes pawn.
Kiki, your move.
Pawn to A6.
Clever, for a pinko Communist.
- Knight to C3.
- Brittany,
The chess club is helping me re-create
World Championship
And it's the only creative outlet I have
This is freaking me out.
This is not you.
You love to dance.
And I know that you think that you're a little rusty right now,
I'll prove it to you.
Let's do a number together.
No. Those days are over.
This is my life now.
Bishop to E3.
It all comes down
Rachel Berry, she represents Broadway,
I'm the future. A pop diva.
I mean, she may be a pop diva,
Broadway musicals of all time.
Why do they call it Broadway
You know, this vote asks the question,
I mean, is it a training ground for-for theme park
You know, the kind of stars that you actually hear on the radio.
I beat Kurt singing this song in our first diva-off.
I am better than her.
I've always been better than her.
Just vote for me.
And let's settle this once and for all time.
Amen.
So, you two are getting hitched?
When's the happy occasion?
Well, we don't know just yet.
We were gonna wait later in the year to set a date.
We're enjoying a long engagement.
Oh, I'm so happy for you.
If I've said it once,
I've said it a million times:
The one thing this country needs more of is teen marriage.
I got you a wedding present.
It's a little hooch.
Oh.
It'll help dull the excruciating pain
Okay, guys, we're having our secret ballot
Puckerman
Actually, Mr. Shue, I was hoping for this number that...
Hold up, hold up,
Private Puckerman.
I'm gonna let you finish,
Mr. Shue, you said that we could redo
Well, then I want to do a dance duet with Brittany.
Hit it.
♪ Well, sometimes
I go out by myself ♪
♪ And I look across the water ♪
♪ And I think of all the things, what you're doing ♪
♪ And in my head
I paint a picture ♪
♪ 'Cause since I've come on home ♪
♪ Well, my body's been a mess ♪
♪ And I've missed your ginger hair ♪
♪ And the way you like to dress ♪
♪ Won't you come on over? ♪
♪ Stop making a fool out of me ♪
♪ Why don't you come on over,
Valerie? ♪
♪ Valerie ♪
♪ Well, sometimes I go out by myself ♪
♪ And I look across the water ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ And I think of all the things, what you're doing ♪
♪ In my head I paint a picture ♪
♪ I paint a picture ♪
♪ 'Cause since
I've come on home ♪
♪ Well, my body's been a mess ♪
♪ And I miss your ginger hair ♪
♪ And the way you like to dress ♪
♪ Oh, won't you come on over? ♪
♪ Stop making a fool out of me ♪
♪ I said, why don't you come on over ♪
♪ Valerie? ♪
♪ Valerie ♪
♪ Why don't you come on over ♪
♪ Valerie? ♪
See? This is who you are.
This is what happens
- when you don't think about it.
- Wow.
I wouldn't want to follow that number,
Well, you know what,
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ Together we stand ♪
♪ I'll be by your side ♪
♪ You know I'll take your hand ♪
♪ And when it gets cold ♪
♪ And it feels like the end ♪
♪ There's no place to go ♪
♪ You know I won't give in ♪
♪ No, I won't give in ♪
♪ Keep ♪
♪ Holding on ♪
♪ 'Cause you know we'll make it through ♪
♪ We'll make it through ♪
♪ Just stay strong ♪
♪ 'Cause you know I'm here for you, I'm here for you ♪
♪ There's nothing you could say ♪
♪ Nothing you could say ♪
♪ Nothing you could do ♪
♪ There's no other way when it comes to the truth ♪
♪ So keep ♪
♪ Holding on ♪
♪ 'Cause you know we'll make it through ♪
♪ We'll make it through ♪
♪ Hear me when I say ♪
♪ When I say I believe ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna change ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna change destiny ♪
♪ Whatever's meant to be ♪
♪ Will work out perfectly ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Keep ♪
♪ Holding on ♪
♪ 'Cause you know we'll make it through ♪
♪ We'll make it through ♪
♪ Just stay strong ♪
♪ 'Cause you know I'm here for you ♪
♪ I'm here for you ♪
♪ There's nothing you could say ♪
♪ Nothing you could say ♪
♪ Nothing you could do ♪
♪ There's no other way when it comes to the truth ♪
♪ So keep ♪
♪ Holding on ♪
♪ 'Cause you know we'll make it through ♪
♪ We'll make it through. ♪
I guess I can still saw your heart.
I loved the song,
I'm crying because
I had actually forgotten about it.
In a couple years...
Well, that's why you gotta keep holding on to your past.
And not be ashamed of it.
I'd rather look forward.
We all love you for who you are.
And I'm in love with Biff.
All right, everybody!
No more drama.
Time to vote
Excuse me, Schuester.
Before we cast another pointless vote
I would like to say
Rachel Berry is the most
- What?
- Can it, troll.
- Santana...
- You have sold
That's not true.
All right, what is his name?
Rick.
Exactly. Thank you.
See, you've all met Rachel, okay?
But I've... I live with her.
Let me tell you what it's like
Someone in that apartment
Kurt, so do the math.
- That's a lie.
- You know what else is a lie?
When you won Prom Queen.
- What?
- Yeah, that's right.
You didn't win, okay?
Everybody just felt really bad for you,
Quinn and I,
You're so cruel, Santana.
I mean, you're only doing this to me
You want to make me feel bad because I'm better than you.
And you're an awful person.
Oh! I feel so much better.
Let's vote.
Well, that Santana rant really brought me back.
You don't even know
I mean, Santana and I
And now it's like no matter where I go
You know, every time a producer
I'm not good enough
God, it's like
Santana is saying it.
Or Puck or Quinn
Sometimes it's even you.
I'm one of your high school ghosts?
It's not necessarily a bad thing.
I just use all of that stuff,
It just makes me sad that you would think
I guess I just...
I don't know, I had this
You were never like them.
You were just always
You know, and I want you to be all big
I just want to be richer...
Oh, don't you think that
Beyoncé and Barbra feel that way?
Girl, I don't know. Ask me when I get my first gold record.
Okay?
Well, I mean,
I will have won
Oh...
Come here.
After the unpleasantness of our last encounter,
I decided to do some deep background
Wikipedia search
You, April Rhodes,
Buddy Leibowitz,
It was that money that you placed into an annuity
That's right.
Well, it didn't last.
In fact, that money ran out six weeks ago.
How?
Will Schuester's profligate spending
I have here a line-item budget
Whoa, whoa, hold-hold on.
Let-let me see that.
I don't know what the problem is,
I'm good for it.
April Rhodes is rich!
No, April Rhodes is under indictment
Oh, snap!
Wait, what?
Well, what April may have neglected to mention
Bernie Madoff.
All of April's assets,
April, is this true?
Gulp.
Sure sounds true, doesn't it?
I'm sorry, Will.
It does appear that
Will, wait! Wait!
- This is yours.
- Yes.
Will, wait!
I can explain...
Explain what, April?
That's you're a pathological liar
Yes, exactly.
You did the worst thing
You gave me hope.
What are you talking about? A tattoo?
It's not that bad.
I mean, it was...
On your lower back?
Ryan Seacrest?
I could get it removed.
There's not a laser big enough.
It's the size of Texas.
You should've told me this weeks ago.
We're in the 20th century.
That doesn't make sense.
- The 21st, almost.
- Is there a problem here?
Puck, go away.
Okay? We're...
Was she always this big of a liar?
I'm coming clean now.
Doesn't that mean something?
Wh... a baby?
I mean, what happens if we got married
Are you crazy?
Was this the loser who knocked you up?
- Yes, yes. Puck is the father.
- Yeah.
I am looking for acceptance here, okay?
This is how I love.
That may be how you
You are the worst kind of hypocrite.
You walk around like you're some
Snow frickin' White, but you're really
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
- You shouldn't have said that.
Let go of my nose!
Ow, God, let go!
Am I bleeding?
Not yet.
You're hurting him! Stop!
Kind of the point!
Knock it off!
Stop!
Help me get him out of here.
Do you have any idea
Look, you can crawl into the trash
I'll be waiting.
All right, everybody.
It's time to get
Y'all can use your left hand for anonymity.
But I'm left-handed.
- Then use a foot.
- Okay.
Dude, who you putting on?
Well, I'm torn.
One is black and one is Jewish.
Okay, that's everybody.
So, um,
Mercedes and I have been talking.
And we both realize that asking you guys to vote
Well, funny enough, they did vote,
And guess what.
You're both equally talented in their eyes.
And mine.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I'd like to apologize.
It's not the first time I've raised someone's hopes
- Just ask all of my A.A. sponsors.
- April?
We just want to spend the rest of the week singing in peace.
But I did do was use the last few hours
Ladies and gentlemen...
Hola, clase.
April, thank you for buttering the floor for me.
You know I like to make an entrance.
Wait, I'm-I'm sorry.
How-how do you two know each other?
Oh, because there's a whole Facebook page
I'm on it, April...
Blaine's brother, Rachel's mom,
Holly...
This is amazing.
Where have you been?
Oh, I've been everywhere.
I quit being a substitute teacher
I like teaching a room full of kids if I know
I'm never gonna see them again,
So, I started my trademark
Holly Holliday Teachin' Pop-Ups.
I just show up at a classroom
Hello!
I'm William Henry Harrison,
America's worst president.
I exterminated a nation of Native Americans,
But I refused to wear a coat to my inauguration,
I accomplished nothing!
There she is!
She just showed up, and she took
Tippy-canoe!
But when I heard
Glee Club was ending,
I ripped off my Pol Pot uniform,
Uh, Holly, you know that we're singing
That's a terrible idea!
Listen, that might be fine for you nerds,
Hit it!
♪ It might seem crazy what I'm about to say ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Sunshine, she's here, you can take a break ♪
♪ I'm a hot-air balloon that could go to space ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ With the air like I don't care, baby, by the way ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
'cause I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel like a room without a roof ♪
♪ Because I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel ♪
♪ Like happiness is the truth ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, because I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you know what happiness is to you ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel ♪
♪ Like that's what you want to do ♪
♪ Here come bad news talking this and that ♪
♪ Come bad news talking this and that ♪
♪ Give me all you got, don't hold back ♪
♪ Don't hold back ♪
♪ Well, I should probably warn you ♪
♪ I'll be just fine ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ No offense to you, don't waste your time ♪
♪ I won't waste your time ♪
♪ Here's why ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel ♪
♪ Like a room without a roof ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel ♪
♪ Like happiness is the truth ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Clap along if you know what happiness is to you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel like that's what you want to do ♪
♪ Ooh, oh, ooh, ooh, ooh, come to me ♪
♪ Bring me down, can't nothing ♪
♪ Bring me down ♪
♪ Your love is too high to bring me down ♪
♪ Can't nothing bring me down ♪
♪ I said I'll tell you now ♪
♪ Bring me down ♪
♪ Can't nothing bring me down ♪
♪ Your love is too high to bring me down ♪
♪ Can't nothing ♪
♪ Bring me down, say ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm happy ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel like ♪
♪ A room without a roof ♪
♪ Without a roof ♪
♪ Clap along if you feel ♪
♪ Like happiness is the truth ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm happy. ♪
He forgave us for what we did, right?
A long time ago.
And we saved him.
Rachel was his soul mate.
Who's yours?
Biff?
He's going back to Yale.
Alone.
This is so not cool.
Okay, they can't just chain you to a calculator
Wait, do those actually exist?
You need to be having a life.
You need to be out in the world
Yeah, I think I'm gonna blow this place, too.
Unless there's a reason for me to stay.
'Cause I know who my soul mate is.
Okay, um...
You don't want me.
I'm terrible at having
I love you.
Just tell me to stay.
'Cause the truth is there's only one guy
It feels really good to be around you.
You make me feel like a girl again.
Like, my body wakes up.
Please don't do this, okay?
I have worked my ass off to get over you.
I really want to be with you, Santana.
I've seen the world, and I'm sure now more than ever
And I'm sure your girlfriend's great,
Just tell me to stay.
Please.
So, it's your choice.
If you want me, I'm here.
Stay.
I want to show you guys something.
All of you that were together from the very beginning
Their new and final resting places.
For as long as McKinley's around,
And have absolutely no idea who they are.
You know what? This is crazy.
Because I could really give two poops about this place,
I know. Why is that?
We were all raised by different parents.
But we grew up together in the glee club.
It's a part of all of us.
Of course you're sad about it.
I don't know, Mr. Schue.
With this and Finn,
I don't have any more pep talks.
I just have you guys.
And the memory of the people on this wall.
My friends.
I mean, we share this special bond.
We're the only ones in the world who-who know
What it felt like to sing together.
To be... to be together.
And what it feels like to say good-bye to it.
I didn't come here to cheer you up.
Just to thank you.
To thank you for going on this ride with me.
All right, come on.
We've still got a few days until, uh,
Sue shuts the lights out on the choir room, so...
I mean, I know we got to finish our wine first.
Mmm.
But when we do, we cannot let
Oh, couldn't have said it better myself.
Holly Holliday...
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com